Contact

toufikaminew@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/taoufik-a-179292211 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Virtual Private Network (VPN)
Voice over IP (VoIP)
Wireless Technologies

Languages

French (Native or Bilingual)

Python (Limited Working)

HTML (Professional Working)

Certifications

CompTIA Security+ (SY0-601)
Cert Prep: 1 Threats, Attacks, and
Vulnerabilities

Windows 10: Administration

Securing Windows Server 2016: Server Hardening Solutions

Securing Windows Server 2019

Windows Server 2019: Manage, Monitor, and Maintain Servers

Taoufik A

System Admin | Technical Support | Customer Service | Server/ Network | Problem-Solving | Hardware/Software Deployment Monitoring/Maintenance/Installation | Project implementation | UX/UI Design|WebDev | Cyber Security

United States

Summary

Security/Technology enthusiast, nerd and a professional individual with extensive experience working as a team player in IT environment as a senior computer engineering/system admin communicating with the Level 1 Service Desk resources, addressing, resolving, monitoring computer problems and questions. Resolve any escalated inquires, requests, and tickets by clients, users, and customers.

2+ years experience in restaurant technology working with systems Aloha, CFC, POS, NBO, MenuLink and various other restaurant systems.

5+ years experience working as a customer service Satisfaction specialist handling customers' questions and concerns. Ensuring high quality customer service. Making sure customers' complaints are handled professionally and accordingly.

Couple years of experience working as a freelancer web designer. Working on clients' websites projects.

Currently transferring my extensive IT skills, experience and knowledge towards specializing in Cyber security and network security besides exploring/learning skills in UX/UI design and software development to make the world a better place through technology

Experience

Clever Programmer
Full Stack Bootcamp Student
January 2021 - Present (5 months)

Springboard Cyber Security Student May 2021 - Present (1 month) HCL Technologies
Desktop Support Specialist
February 2020 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Freelancer.com
Web Designer
January 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)

Tenet Healthcare
Taleo HealthStream Tier II Remote Support Specialist
August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

NEC Corporation Level 2 Support Technician October 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Pei Wei Tier III Restaurant Support Analyst January 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 4 months)

Brinker International
Client Support Professional
January 2017 - January 2018 (1 year 1 month)

D&H Distributing
Cloud Client Support Professional
January 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 5 months)

EarthLink Internet
Desktop Support Engineer
January 2013 - January 2016 (3 years 1 month)

Zenith Reading and Learning Center
Onsite Computer Tech
September 2008 - July 2013 (4 years 11 months)

Education

Springboard

· (May 2021 - November 2021)

University at Buffalo

Master of Technology - MTech, Computer Science · (2016 - 2018)

Franklin University

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology Project Management · (2009 - 2013)

The Ohio State University

Associate's degree, Information Technology · (2007 - 2009)